Mom!
Mom...
- This...
- Mom...
Isn't it?
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, shaman.
To live... I did that.
I did it because I wanted to live
open the door
You little devil, open the door!
Open the door!
You evil bastard!
Is your brother a good person?
Huh?
Are you a good person?
Uh...
Well?
I'm a bad person
Huh?
No evil spirits
I need to find the demon, I need to get rid of it right away.
I can't go
What?
I can't go.
Do you know what evil spirits can do?
General Dongcheon was the last.
He just killed his 100th person.
He has become an evil spirit, now!
Let go!
- You won't let it go?
- Write!
- Let go!
- Chloride
Let go
So is there a way?
Let go!
Don't die with Bongsu.
Is there a way!
Let go!
I'm trying to save you!
I was trying to save you
What happened to my mom...
I...
Are you really...
I hate it so much
I will protect it
I will definitely protect it
Please listen to me!
Mansik!
Fairy of Heaven and Earth...
Where is the heavenly fairy?
I don't know if this is a good thing to do now
Where is she now?
what? where are you?
Seongya
Where are you?
Is it a dream, a dream?
why?
Am I so pretty that it feels like a dream?
Since I woke up, let’s go on a date quickly.
one, two, three
You're filming!
Eight
Done
Wow
- Did you do it?
- Yes
let's go
But that...
Where has Bongsu gone?
I can't feel him anymore
went
- You went?
- Yes
where and how?
Shhh
If you say it, Bongsu will come again.
Flower Doryeong
Mansik, are you there?
Hong Man-sik!
You don’t have to let me go, okay?
Listen to me, Mansik!
Hong Man-sik!
Aunt!
Why do you keep calling me?
Mansik
you don't know
Even the fairy of heaven and earth doesn’t know
What?
Evil spirits do not bring disaster
The self itself is a disaster
It won't cause disaster
If the evil spirit stays
I'm starting to get sick
Seongya
At first the plants died
Then the animal dies
In the end, people die
We need to stop the fairy of heaven and earth
He doesn't even know what he's doing.
no
Chunghwa, I know everything.
He knows everything
The one in the vending machine
Did you bring everything with you?
No, I don't know what you'll like
I brought everything first.
Don't you know what I like?
Eight
I like you
you are my first love
Ah...
- Me too...
- and
this is my first kiss
I will definitely be back before graduation ceremony
Let’s go now, Bongsu.
mother
I'm in the dark, I can't see front or back
That I am walking correctly
How do you know?
I have to take the lead
I don't know what's coming
I'm walking in the front
Then
Does it walk properly?
You can protect it
things behind my back
mother
I'll go right
I'll walk straight
I will definitely... protect it.
Bongsu, stand behind me from now on.
Why? I want to stand next to you?
Please stand back and watch closely.
Are you walking straight?
Sure, whatever
I will definitely be back before graduation ceremony
Seongya
Seongya!
Seong-ah... Seong-ah
Park Seong-ah!
Seongya!
Seongah Park
Park Seong-ah...
Why am I a senior in high school?
Seongah leaves
We became seniors in high school
What is it, what is it, what is it, what is it?
Hey Jinwoong!
Although the class was divided
We ate together
Come out quickly!
- What is this?
-What is it? Come out quickly.
What, what, what!
Come out quickly
What are you doing now?
Do you want to die, huh?
Ah
Don't smoke, okay?
I laugh often even when there is nothing special going on
and cowherd
guy
Oh my
Oh my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my?
Good job, really Gyeonwoo.
Uh, uh, huh?
It's awesome
Bae Gyeon-woo was doing well, really.
It's a machine, it's a machine
goodbye
thank you
That guy is so suspicious
There was a time when I was quietly followed
It's Heena
Congratulations on your discharge
Do you still hate me?
Yeah
I'll probably hate you for the rest of my life?
you know
I set fire to the dorm that day.
Actually, it's me
It's too late to turn back
Because I wasn't properly punished
I'll probably live with punishment forever
How come?
Why didn't you say it was me until the end?
If it weren't for me
You wouldn't have done that.
you are still foolish
I'm still a coward
Is that so?
But
now we
Let's be happy
Are you really
I want you to be happy
Why?
Because I'm your first friend?
Yeah
and
I met my second friend
He taught me
It's okay to be happy...
So did you feel happy?
Give me your phone
Among the many bad things I did to you
I think this is the worst
They didn’t even let me save my name
Don't contact me anymore
If you want to be happy, you have to do that first.
That...
archery
Are you going to do it again?
yes
See you at the competition
Gyeonwoo is alone like a traitor
Even if I secretly meet Seong-ah
So much so that it doesn't matter
I missed Seongah so much
This is Hwamok High School
We conclude the 76th graduation ceremony.
one, two, three
Ah, Dad, vertically, not horizontally.
Dad, come quickly and take a picture with us.
It's graduation!
and
We just waited for the graduation ceremony
one, two, three
one more time
high school graduation ceremony
I want to go to the university entrance ceremony
I want to take a commemorative photo holding a bouquet of flowers.
This is Seongah’s wish.
Wake up, let me take a picture.
Take a picture with this
Hold it horizontally like this
one, two, three
Wait a minute
Let's raise it just a little bit more
This much, a little bigger
- No, this is right.
- No.
one, two
Don’t you know that this guy has good proportions?
- No...
-A little bigger? Just a little more
No, what's the big deal?
Do you have a bad memory?
It's here
It's here, it's like this
Is it too small?
Just a little more
I have to upload it
I'll take a picture
I don't know, it's around here.
They said they would take a picture of it
give it
Take one, two, three
one
Two...
three
Seongya, wait.
I'll go now
It’s been a while?
Are you still scared when you see me?
I'm excited
god
It's up?
If the temple loses its owner
It's like this
Things that have lost their use quickly become worn out.
crumbles
Fairy god
I completely left the shaman
That means
It means the shaman is dead.
No?
Seongah is not dead.
That's right
He's not dead
That's why it's strange
What are you talking about?
We use harmony
Have you ever been connected?
If he dies
You and I get to know each other
When you appear in a dream wearing white clothes
To say my last goodbye
But it's strange
I got excited
I won't die
The evil spirit attached to his body
What kind of harmony are you doing?
How to find Seong-ah...
I need to find it as soon as possible
Before seriously harming people
What harm does it do?
Seong-ah hurts people?
Do you think Seong-ah is like you? yes?
Do you think I was that kind of kid from the beginning?
This won't fit
I'll have to find something else
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, you handsome bastard!
You, you, you, you'll be punished for doing this, you!
Heavenly punishment
Are you already receiving it?
uh?
Uh, huh?
Hey, hey, stop, stop!
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
Uh...
I...
on that arrow
Wind it up like this and shoot it.
If you're lucky, you might catch a ghost
Thank you, I will definitely find Seong-ah with this.
Hey, it's okay, just don't say anything.
Just go quickly
Yes, next time
I will come with Seong-ah.
Go
I came as you said
I gave it to you as I asked.
I'll pay for the amulet
Come again
Write it again
Is this correct, not the value of the amulet that is the problem?
Isn’t Handsome also becoming dangerous?
Did I order it?
he's doing it
You saw it too
He needs to do something now
Okay, I'll call you back.
May I ask what you do?
yes
Among family members
What can I do if I hide it?
If you do evil things, the power of evil spirits becomes stronger.
I have been chasing the Heaven and Earth Fairy for over a year.
I couldn't find a single hair.
The moment I thought I found it
I committed evil deeds and got away with it many times.
Because I couldn't bear the evil deeds
A fairy god has appeared.
But we still have him
A child in whom an evil spirit resided
That energy still remains
Even though the evil spirit has left
Even though there is no excitement
see and hear ghosts
A kid who can talk to ghosts
maybe we
I might be able to find the Heaven and Earth Fairy.
With the power of that persistent relationship
Student Gyeonwoo took this
There is no way you would refuse, right?
Just be honest and ask for help.
Why so much trouble?
If I find it, I will kill you.
Will you cooperate?
yes?
To exorcise evil spirits
heaven and earth fairy
I have to die
I, by any chance
Do you know this shaman?
I think you know?
Then
Shall I tell you everything I know?
To worship evil spirits
Looking for a faceless ghost?
A deaf ear?
They need to be treated kind of harshly.
Literally no face
So the person who makes the face
Being the owner
Because they gave me a new face
now i am your master
Where is he?
Shuuuuut
Oh my
Hey, you guy, Bae Gyeon-woo
You nigga, you, you
Do you have anything to say to the teacher?
sorry
No, what happened?
once in two months
You can't come to practice, right? uh?
Dude, all you have to do is win a gold medal?
You and why this fake day
Are you getting caught while shooting an archery in the mountains?
To the police, that too in the middle of the night?
now!
Just keep talking
Talk to me!
I need to know why
I'm not going to shield, are you?
Hey, you guy
If you continue like this
The association takes disciplinary action against you.
- Coach
- Uh
I promise to come back
Can you forget the woman who left you?
the first kiss
It's not going to be a goodbye, is it?
But anyway
It doesn't even appear in my dreams
Now I see the world he saw, right?
But
Something like this...
As I live, I keep watching
I wonder how you could smile like that
I wish I knew it would be like this
Forcing a smile
Should I say I don't want to see it or not?
Actually, your smile was very pretty.
yes
There's just one person missing
The whole world is just gray, right?
huh?
That's how love is, love
Love...
That's how it is
Now I'm your master
Recite exactly what you just said to him.
Don't make a single mistake
Find the way to paradise
I am reincarnated in India.
3, 2, 1
3, 2, 1, 3, 2...
Everyone
You have to go to a good place
What are you doing so hard?
Are you praying to 100 vengeful spirits?
When I go to the underworld, I go to King Yeomra.
I just need to pray once
Hey
don't disturb
before I kill you
Are you done with ghosts?
let's go
Hey
Let go, won’t you let go of this?
If it were you, would you let go?
I don't want to hurt you
Let it go quickly
Stop the show
Let's go quietly
Go!
Go quickly, Seong-ya!
No, no!
Stop, no!
What are you doing?
What are you doing!
At the Archery Association
It's a shameful act
It was my last chance to catch it.
you now
Do you even know what the world has solved?
If the shaman didn't make a beacon
- I didn't have to solve anything...
- So now
I'm trying to make it right!
Seongah
I wish it was Seongah
I don't do this carelessly.
Not in a way that hurts
You must have found another way
So
Look for a shaman too, like Seongah.
What should I do because I feel sad?
Now there is no other way than exorcism...
no
I can't even do an exorcism.
Since there is no way to catch it
Hey Gyeonwoo
What happens when he comes to see you in the future?
The only time they come to kill you?
In the future, if
If you ever encounter one, run away.
run away and call me
That's the only way you can live
Yes, in the case of interviews
Delivered to you in advance
Because it will be conducted mainly through questionnaires.
don't be too nervous
Please proceed with ease.
Hello, I am
This is Bae Gyeon-woo.
Yes, I am a recurve athlete.
I'm happy
Uh... it's the best
Ah, why can’t I speak like this?
Hey, hands down, uh
Hands down
- That’s right
- Yes, it's good.
Then, Bae Gyeon-woo’s dream is
Maybe an Olympic gold medal?
Ah
Olympic gold medal is now my goal.
I have a different dream
Ah, my dream
Meeting my first love again
Wow, suddenly the interview was very interesting.
It's getting romantic.
Then between the gold medal and first love
What if you had to choose?
First love
Young, it’s a video message, right?
I miss you
Seongah Park
child
It hits me hard
No, wait a minute, Jiho.
Oh, hey, please stop!
- Oh, really.
-What are you doing, ow!
Stop it, really.
I'm sorry...
Surprised
Please knock
What is it? Why are you here?
this is my house
IC
If you're going to come, please contact me in advance, okay?
It's my house where I live alone
You want me to contact you and come?
Are you thinking of living here?
Have you packed your bags?
Yeah, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Hey, that's right!
Do you eat dinner at home?
Um... watching?
Oh, eat at home, huh?
I'll cook something delicious for you
Wow, hey
If you have time, fix this
Let's go, rest
Come back
Yes, aunt.
He passed away?
yes
Find me... I'll see you.
big old man
You two prayed for me until the day you left.
Not only you
He will protect Seong-ah at the same time.
For the time being, I think your body is glass.
Live carefully
You can do it, right?
Let's try it
In the fairy’s room
Rather than leaving it alone
What Gyeonwoo student has
I thought it would get better
yes
I will take good care of it
I hope you are doing well.
I guess so?
Come back slowly
yes
It would be a waste of you
If it was the Joseon Dynasty
He must have received a virtuous woman’s letter from the country.
Oh, because I’m a man, is it 10 divisions?
You're still the same
It's good
Are you being sarcastic?
You did it first.
What is your dream?
Did you dream anything?
yes
Is there time in your answer?
Suspiciously?
Ah, when I come to a dream
Are you saying he's already dead?
Yes, thank you
I just need to go pick up the body.
There's no use looking at it that way
Now it's me who's on your side, not him
If you meet me in a dream, be sure to ask where it is
We need to retrieve the body and clean up the place.
If you meet me in real life, I always run away.
contact me
Contact us...
What if you don’t like it?
Hey Gyeonwoo
When did you
Did you contact me because you like me?
Don’t do it if you don’t want to.
It would be nice to see grandma early.
I came
You arrived quickly?
Just wait a moment
I don't eat it
Hey, it’s the sixth form?
What is your dream?
Did you dream anything?
When I meet you in a dream
Be sure to ask where it is
Seongah's dream
Dream about Seong-ah
Earlier, to the shaman Yeomhwa,
There's something I didn't say
A dream I dreamed at some point
Here again
A 3rd grade classroom with an unknown number of classes.
strange class lesson
Jiho and I are in the same class.
We were in different classes in third grade.
Seongya
Well... right?
In your place
This is what the classroom looks like
well drawn
Hey Gyeonwoo
Hey, Bae Gyeonwoo wake up.
Is it a newborn? Just fall asleep, okay?
Wake up, let's go out and eat
Hey, have you ever done that?
I'm dreaming
Feeling like it's not my dream?
By all means...
Feeling like I'm in someone else's dream
our cowherd
You're talking so much nonsense now?
me
Sometimes I feel like I'm in a dream
The voice doesn't come out
Seongah, dream
Oh my, oh my, oh my!
Oh, why do you keep hiding? Just meet me
What if I meet you and harm you?
No, it's just a dream. What harm can it do?
uh? Why is a dream a dream?
Isn’t it a dream because you can do whatever you want?
And even if I cause harm, I won't do it
Why are you causing this?
Because you never know
It looks like Gyeonwoo and Jiho are living together, right?
I guess they are still close
It went well
Star, be close or not
Is it because Gyeonwoo sat down and went away?
It's warm
No, but why is he
Would you like to sit in someone else's seat?
Are you a pervert?
Bongsuya
I have enough of this
It's enough to see Gyeonwoo like this sometimes.
Did you draw that?
Wow, well drawn
That...
This is what you were drawing just now
Ah
That's right
Ah, I have to finish drawing it.
Seongah doesn’t appear.
Seongah, how do you know it was a dream?
I just know
Just...
I know
So that...
Where did I get this picture of the beach?
Don't talk about dreams
What kind of beach again? huh?
I went to that beach...
The beach...
Huh?
This guy
Curse me?
No matter how good I am at using talismans
I can't use this, I can't use this, I can't use this.
This guy is a dog, huh?
Young & Handsome, Heaven and Earth Fairy’s First Love
So
Bad luck, Mr.
Hey, if you're frustrated, do it yourself.
You are strong
too strong
If I curse, he dies
But what about Heaven and Earth Fairy?
Are you still with me?
If I tell you, will you curse me?
Let's not talk, let's not talk
Oh, really
I thought you wouldn't do it, tsk
Going
Already?
Hey, it's bad for me if I stay here too long
Do you want to die quickly?
While I wasn't watching, I became even more of a bitch.
Um...
What is your name? How are you finding it?
Hey, Mr.
If I had found it well, I would have already achieved Buddhahood.
Would I come to meet someone like you?
Ah, so annoying
Ah! I want to go quickly
Because I keep looking at your face
I'm trying to become more unlucky
Wow, this guy is crazy, since he came!
Hey, are you there?
- Flower spirit!
- What is it, a tiger?
Sir, are you inside?
Uh, uh, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Hey, come here
I'm in here
Hey, wait a minute!
If you go in there, won't you die?
Don’t you know Crown Prince Sado?
I don't know, shut up and go in, quickly.
Quick!
- Boy...
- Wait a minute!
Oh my gosh
- Shhh
- Uh
Uh, come in
You don't have to work that hard.
God needs to come down again
Before that
No matter how much I clean it up
It just gets more and more gloomy.
I know
But if you just leave it alone
I feel uncomfortable
Thank you to my aunt for her hard work
Even if you think about it
God should come quickly
Until the day the old man passes away
It looks like you prayed for me.
Old man
Did you know that I would be grateful for this?
I think you're grateful?
What is it all about?
Ah
big old man
These are the items of people who prayed for me until the end.
This is a fairy's item.
Write it, isn’t it?
I used it as a human talisman.
Is it Gyeonwoo’s student stuff?
In that case
It's right to give it to Gyeonwoo.
Um...
Only then will the broken relationship
Because we can connect again
Yes?
Oh, no, I was thinking about something else for a moment.
Seongah
If you appear in a dream wearing white clothes
It's a dead deal.
We used to be
powerfully with magic
I have been connected
If something goes wrong, I'll know in my dreams
Yeah, uh
I'm having a dream, yeah
Ah, man, it’s frustrating.
Lady, I'm dying, really.
But I
I'm sure, Seong-ah, you're safe.
That's just how I feel
It's strange but it's something
I feel like it's close, even now
I feel like I'm right next to you
Uh...
Oh, and when I dream
I feel Seongah
Very vividly
Hey, when are you leaving?
What did you just say?
uh? what?
What are you talking about?
I didn't hear anything?
No, obviously...
It's a dream where no one comes out
I can't see it
I think Seong-ah is there.
What are you talking about over there...
Over there?
Oh, there's nothing there
there's nothing there
This, this sound
- Oh, I think there is one.
- No, there isn't any.
Hey, hey, no, no, no
- I don't know
- No, what is there...
Ouch!
Oh!
Wow, Mr.!
There's a lot of dirty talk, really.
Seongya
Ah!
That bitch, that thing
Hey!
hey!
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Ah, really, hey!
hey!
Stop, stop, stop, stop
Mr. Lee...
IC
I don't know either
Oh no, it doesn't change
Ah... Ai, ai, yaisi?
Seong-ah... hey?
Hey
Do you think it's Seonga?
The shaman’s soul bowl is broken.
No work is an equivalent exchange
If one life fades away
One life blooms
Please die instead of the shaman.
Please do me a favor.
What should I do?
When you woke up
Everything will already be over
Isn't it so unfair that I'm the only one who dies?
Who is it? Only you die
Where is Yeomhwa now?
I will let you go without any pain.
You can't be with me
Hello